[
  {
    "question": "ア",
    "answer": "A",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "イ",
    "answer": "I",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "ウ",
    "answer": "U",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "エ",
    "answer": "E",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "オ",
    "answer": "O",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 5
  },
  {
    "question": "カ",
    "answer": "Ka",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "キ",
    "answer": "Ki",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "ク",
    "answer": "Ku",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "ケ",
    "answer": "Ke",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "コ",
    "answer": "Ko",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "サ",
    "answer": "Sa",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "シ",
    "answer": "Shi",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 12
  },
  {
    "question": "ス",
    "answer": "Su",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "セ",
    "answer": "Se",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 14
  },
  {
    "question": "ソ",
    "answer": "So",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 15
  },
  {
    "question": "タ",
    "answer": "Ta",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 16
  },
  {
    "question": "チ",
    "answer": "Chi",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 17
  },
  {
    "question": "ツ",
    "answer": "Tsu",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 18
  },
  {
    "question": "テ",
    "answer": "Te",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 19
  },
  {
    "question": "ト",
    "answer": "To",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 20
  },
  {
    "question": "ナ",
    "answer": "Na",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 21
  },
  {
    "question": "ニ",
    "answer": "Ni",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 22
  },
  {
    "question": "ヌ",
    "answer": "Nu",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 23
  },
  {
    "question": "ネ",
    "answer": "Ne",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 24
  },
  {
    "question": "ノ",
    "answer": "No",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 25
  },
  {
    "question": "ハ",
    "answer": "Ha",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 26
  },
  {
    "question": "ヒ",
    "answer": "Hi",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 27
  },
  {
    "question": "フ",
    "answer": "Fu",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 28
  },
  {
    "question": "ヘ",
    "answer": "He",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 29
  },
  {
    "question": "ホ",
    "answer": "Ho",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 30
  },
  {
    "question": "マ",
    "answer": "Ma",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 31
  },
  {
    "question": "ミ",
    "answer": "Mi",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 32
  },
  {
    "question": "ム",
    "answer": "Mu",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 33
  },
  {
    "question": "メ",
    "answer": "Me",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 34
  },
  {
    "question": "モ",
    "answer": "Mo",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 35
  },
  {
    "question": "ヤ",
    "answer": "Ya",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 36
  },
  {
    "question": "ユ",
    "answer": "Yu",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 37
  },
  {
    "question": "ヨ",
    "answer": "Yo",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 38
  },
  {
    "question": "ラ",
    "answer": "Ra",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 39
  },
  {
    "question": "リ",
    "answer": "Ri",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 40
  },
  {
    "question": "ル",
    "answer": "Ru",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 41
  },
  {
    "question": "レ",
    "answer": "Re",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 42
  },
  {
    "question": "ロ",
    "answer": "Ro",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 43
  },
  {
    "question": "ワ",
    "answer": "Wa",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 44
  },
  {
    "question": "ヲ",
    "answer": "O (Wo)",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 45
  },
  {
    "question": "ン",
    "answer": "Nn",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 46
  },
  {
    "question": "ガ",
    "answer": "Ga",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 47
  },
  {
    "question": "ギ",
    "answer": "Gi",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 48
  },
  {
    "question": "グ",
    "answer": "Gu",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 49
  },
  {
    "question": "ゲ",
    "answer": "Ge",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 50
  },
  {
    "question": "ゴ",
    "answer": "Go",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 51
  },
  {
    "question": "ザ",
    "answer": "Za",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 52
  },
  {
    "question": "ジ",
    "answer": "Ji",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 53
  },
  {
    "question": "ズ",
    "answer": "Zu",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 54
  },
  {
    "question": "ゼ",
    "answer": "Ze",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 55
  },
  {
    "question": "ゾ",
    "answer": "Zo",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 56
  },
  {
    "question": "ダ",
    "answer": "Da",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 57
  },
  {
    "question": "ヂ",
    "answer": "Ji",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 58
  },
  {
    "question": "ヅ",
    "answer": "Tzu",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 59
  },
  {
    "question": "デ",
    "answer": "De",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 60
  },
  {
    "question": "ド",
    "answer": "Do",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 61
  },
  {
    "question": "バ",
    "answer": "Ba",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 62
  },
  {
    "question": "ビ",
    "answer": "Bi",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 63
  },
  {
    "question": "ブ",
    "answer": "Bu",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 64
  },
  {
    "question": "ベ",
    "answer": "Be",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 65
  },
  {
    "question": "ボ",
    "answer": "Bo",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 66
  },
  {
    "question": "パ",
    "answer": "Pa",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 67
  },
  {
    "question": "ピ",
    "answer": "Pi",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 68
  },
  {
    "question": "プ",
    "answer": "Pu",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 69
  },
  {
    "question": "ペ",
    "answer": "Pe",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 70
  },
  {
    "question": "ポ",
    "answer": "Po",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 71
  }
]